https://www.nurserecruiter.com/privacy

Log In
Register
Privacy Policy
NurseRecruiter.com is committed to protecting your privacy.
This Statement of Privacy applies to the NurseRecruiter.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the NurseRecruiter.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
If you choose to create an account on our site(s) as a job seeker or employer, NurseRecruiter.com collects personally identifiable information provided by you, such as your resume, e-mail address, name, home or work address and telephone number.
You may also choose to browse our site "anonymously" by not creating an account or logging in.
When you access NurseRecruiter.com via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.
Use of your Personal Information
NurseRecruiter.com collects and uses your personal information to operate the NurseRecruiter.com Web site and deliver the services you have requested. NurseRecruiter.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NurseRecruiter.com and its affiliates.
When you permit us to do so, NurseRecruiter.com may share your personal and/or company information with trusted third parties for the purpose of matching job seekers with employers and staffing companies.
At any time, you may permanently or temporarily suspend the sharing of such information by logging into your account and editing your profile and preferences to disable your profile.
NurseRecruiter.com may also share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, or provide customer support.
All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NurseRecruiter.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
NurseRecruiter.com Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NurseRecruiter.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NurseRecruiter.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NurseRecruiter.com, or the public.
Cookies and Web Beacons
NurseRecruiter.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
Some of our advertising partners may also use cookies and web beacons on our site.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on NurseRecruiter.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to NurseRecruiter.com and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Security of your Personal Information
NurseRecruiter.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. NurseRecruiter.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Privacy policies and practices of external web sites
NurseRecruiter.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of third party Web sites linked to from NurseRecruiter.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. NurseRecruiter.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the NurseRecruiter.com and NurseRecruiter.com family of Web sites.
Changes to this Statement
NurseRecruiter.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NurseRecruiter.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NurseRecruiter.com is protecting your information.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on January 12, 2012
Contact Information
NurseRecruiter.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy and practices, please contact us.
NurseRecruiter.com113 Cherry St. #26760Seattle, WA 98104
Contact us by email
Telephone: 1-800-243-3407
Nursing Jobs
Privacy Policy
